Good morning!
Morning!
What's up?
See ya!
I'm gonna say it!
I'm gonna...
Today's the day!
I'm gonna say it!
I'm gonna...
Morning!
Hey!
Hmm?
You have something to say?
Oh, um...
Never mind.
Hey!
Now I wanna know!
What is it?
Just say it!
Can you not tell me it here?
Here?
Now talk!
Um...
Good morning!
Hey, Ichikawa!
Morning!
What is going on here?
Bonus Dangerous!
blood type quiz it's pop quiz time can you tell me what my blood type is why do you ask
come on try and guess i doubt you can tell though she's the stereotypical type o but if she's acting
all confident maybe that's not it would the complete opposite be type a although she could
be type b wait but in my experience type b's like my sister never want to bring up their blood type
which makes sense since they're unfairly looked down on screw anyone who judges people based on
their damn blood type bet i could trick her into telling me more just so you know i am a b whoa
the step of genius she fell for it no one would call themselves a genius so that means i've got it
you are type a nice try i'm also genius a b right this is yamada we're talking about
we're the same type no i was just kidding i'm not type a b what then what type are you
can we drop this whole conversation it doesn't make any difference anyway
there are way more than just four personality types in the world
no one outside japan even cares about this stuff oh i know you're type b right
bonus dangers
evil powers
i'll be taller before you know it true junior high is that time and all thanks mom
i look like i can use evil powers
i totally made it a three-pointer wow nice work talk about luck although didn't do much from there
i'm afraid didn't even touch the ball again so can't brag much a kobayashi miracle good work all
the same wouldn't be a miracle if i pulled it off every time though could you even do that
i forgot something you go ahead all right then
step step step step step step what are you doing i thought maybe you borrowed someone's
it looks like you're trying to mug me right now all right give me your hand
this is off the record
if we get caught i'd be in lots of trouble it's no good don't worry so much
there what'd i tell you
it's empty anyway
bonus dangers
favorite hairstyle
apparently guys like ponytails more than any other hairstyle
according to moeko
doesn't it depend on the person
okay if that's it then what kind of hairstyle do you like
huh
ponytails are great and all but there's so much more than that
like pigtails or bob cuts and it's hard to say no to short hair too
i gotta stop the more i think on it the more i like them all
how am i supposed to choose
you're really thinking this over
i mean anything would look good on you
oh no i wasn't fishing for a compliment
i just wanted to know what you liked best
bonus dangers
in between class
all right better get moving
oh
huh
i think i left something in class
you left everything
what's up
oh
i'll hold that for you
what's going on here
oh
dayama
watch out too
i'm waiting for a friend
a friend
are you in the science lab next
we're headed that way too
let's go together
this is bad
me
yamada and those two all together sounds like absolute hell
oh
i actually have to go to the office first before heading to class i'm afraid
sorry
got yourself into more trouble
you ought to be careful
figures
she probably doesn't want people to know she's headed to class with me
come on
wait we are going to class together
bonus dangers
hey ichikawa
would you kill me if i became a zombie
yeah
of course
what
you have to take out the head to kill a zombie right
uh
okay
well
what if i was still like conscious or something
hmm
the classic dilemma
anyone who doesn't go through with it dies
you have to do it quickly
you think you really could
give me a break
you can't go outside
so you're a talker huh
do i have a gun
good grief
i need to do this
i need to do this fast
but bang
took you long enough to do it
bang
wait why
if yamada goes
so do i
bonus dangers
hey
what are you doing now
nothing
what
do you think i'm doing
oh
don't know
guess
bonus dangers
shopping with sis
wow
this is really nice
i bet yamada would look great in it
well
wanna die
are you ready
hmm
if this were yamada
i'll take the steak lovers combo with jumbo fries
and pancakes with strawberry sauce too
you want the kids menu
shut up
stop that pickles
come on
you like it
gosh you're so silly
here
say ah
if yamada had a boyfriend
would she be like that too
i bet she would
here
ah
i mean the way you were staring at them
i figured you wanted that
i'm going to kill you
bonus dangers
meat buns
oh
which one are you getting
i'm going for the pizza one
me too then
huh
hey wait
then i'll get the regular one instead
doesn't want to get the same as me huh
is something the matter
i just sort of blindly went along and followed you in
but i've never snacked on the way home
really
awesome
what is
nothing
i hope no one from school passes by
i think the staff here will rat us out at the school
oh
that's so good
hey
no one's gonna come
that's not the point
see
so is it good
yeah
i guess
right
aren't you glad we got different ones
i might
die
tomorrow
bonus dangers
nice scent
uh
empty
this is khanas
but no one will know
it smells like a flowery girl in here
you're right
everyone knows
that was rough
smell should almost be gone though
weird
just me
or does something smell real nice
not her too
like something yummy
i don't want her getting the wrong idea though
better explain the situation
see i accidentally used khanas shampoo
smells like they're having curry here
i accidentally used khanas shampoo
let me see here
oh yeah
but we had jim today so i can't really tell
bonus dangers
oh hell yeah
take that big old member of mine
gross
and shake it through
this just isn't coming out
this sucks
can't wait to go home
you know they should really pay people to clean this
okay
wanna skip out
that's enough
what why
can it
that's sexual harassment you know
how do you figure
but if no one actually does this
then it will just stay dirty
great that worked
the rest looks pretty clean too
our cleaning time is over now
it's not skipping you for that already
sheesh
hey
where to
huh
i don't know
i guess somewhere out of sight would be best
why's that
what
they're cleaning so we'd be in the way
oh yeah
true
bonus dangers
what time do you go to bed
normally
around one
that's late
someone's bad
right
you
11 30
later than that already
that's your fault
bonus dangers
zombie games
hmm
you think i could kill you if you became a zombie
like you're all nasty
sure
why couldn't you
i've got a bad feeling
then let's try it out
i knew it
fine
come on do it already
what i am
wait really
well now that i think about it
this is normal for me
sorry
but hey how would i figure out whether you became a zombie or not
i mean what would be the signs
don't know
i guess maybe it could be by your stinky smell or something
or maybe even by your heartbeat
it would be dangerous to get too close though
oh yeah that's true
how about whether or not you can say my name
not that
what
why not
because
well sometimes
they remember
well then
i couldn't kill you
bonus dangers
bye bye
me saying bye bye is weird
too weird
what now
what do i do
see ya
later
yeah
see you tomorrow
yamada
tomorrow's saturday
bonus dangers
you